<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>TextProbe</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on TextProbe</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2024 05:02:05 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>High Frequency Polling Summary</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/high-frequency-polling-summary/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2024 05:02:05 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/high-frequency-polling-summary/</guid>
      <description>Summary This study explores the potential of online surveys, even those with skewed demographics, to accurately measure public opinion. The authors demonstrate their method by analyzing an Xbox poll of US voters in the 2012 election. By applying statistical adjustments, their estimates align closely with actual results, suggesting non-representative polls can be surprisingly accurate, offering advantages like speed, cost, and real-time tracking of public sentiment.&#xA;Key Points The paper is about using non-representative polling, such as opt-in online surveys, to accurately and continuously track public opinion, with proper statistical adjustment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 14:50:02 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/about/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to TextProbe: Your Ultimate Solution for Understanding Your Customers Our Mission TextProbe is a SaaS platform designed to assist marketers and businesses in gaining deeper insights into their customers through advanced text mining capabilities. Our goal is to empower organizations of all sizes to harness the power of cutting-edge tools for natural language processing (NLP) and natural language understanding (NLU) without the need for extensive in-house expertise. We believe in democratizing AI-driven text analysis to foster innovation and drive growth for every business.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get in Touch</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 14:50:02 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/contact/</guid>
      <description>Curious about how text mining can benefit your business? Our team is here to help, whether you&amp;rsquo;re just getting started or need expert assistance with TextProbe. We can guide you through the process, answer your questions, and show you how to unlock the power of text data.&#xA;We&amp;rsquo;re passionate about helping businesses succeed. Let&amp;rsquo;s collaborate and use proven methods to improve your text-based campaigns and drive results. We look forward to hearing from you!</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
