<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>TextProbe</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on TextProbe</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2024 11:38:40 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Ops as a Job</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/job-title-ops/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2024 11:38:40 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/job-title-ops/</guid>
      <description>What is DevOps In the current market, various operations (ops) positions are available, but the most prevalent one, especially with the rise of Agile, is DevOps. Originally defined as &amp;ldquo;Developers Do Operations,&amp;rdquo; this concept is reflected in tools like Terraform and Bicep. These tools aim to eliminate handoffs and anti-patterns by allowing developers to use templates and budgets, enabling them to create what they need without dependencies on elements Agile seeks to remove.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High Frequency Polling Summary</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/high-frequency-polling-summary/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2024 05:02:05 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/high-frequency-polling-summary/</guid>
      <description>Summary This study explores the potential of online surveys, even those with skewed demographics, to accurately measure public opinion. The authors demonstrate their method by analyzing an Xbox poll of US voters in the 2012 election. By applying statistical adjustments, their estimates align closely with actual results, suggesting non-representative polls can be surprisingly accurate, offering advantages like speed, cost, and real-time tracking of public sentiment.&#xA;Key Points The paper is about using non-representative polling, such as opt-in online surveys, to accurately and continuously track public opinion, with proper statistical adjustment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 14:50:02 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/about/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to TextProbe: Your Ultimate Solution for Text Minning Our Mission TextProbe&amp;rsquo;s is a SaaS maintained by Edwardes LLC to advanced text mining capabilities, ensuring that businesses of all sizes can seamlessly leverage state-of-the-art tools for natural language processing (NLP) without requiring extensive in-house expertise. We believe in enabling every organization, regardless of scale, to unlock the potential of AI-driven text analysis for innovation and growth.&#xA;What Sets Us Apart SMB-Oriented Development Expertise: Our team is composed of individuals with extensive experience in developing tools tailored specifically for small and medium-sized businesses, addressing the unique challenges faced by SMBs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get in Touch</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 14:50:02 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/contact/</guid>
      <description>Curious about how text mining can benefit your business? Our team is here to help, whether you&amp;rsquo;re just getting started or need expert assistance with TextProbe. We can guide you through the process, answer your questions, and show you how to unlock the power of text data.&#xA;We&amp;rsquo;re passionate about helping businesses succeed. Let&amp;rsquo;s collaborate and use proven methods to improve your text-based campaigns and drive results. We look forward to hearing from you!</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
