<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>TextProbe</title>
    <link>https://textprobe.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on TextProbe</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 18:38:04 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://textprobe.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Opened Quetion Powered by Natural Language Processing</title>
      <link>https://textprobe.io/posts/opened-and-nlpu/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 18:38:04 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://textprobe.io/posts/opened-and-nlpu/</guid>
      <description>Unleashing the Power of Open-Ended Questions in Surveys: A TextProbe Perspective In the realm of survey research, the debate between open-ended and close-ended questions has long been a topic of discussion. Over the years, numerous studies have highlighted the richness of responses garnered from open-ended questions, contrasting them with the more constrained nature of close-ended queries. Authors such as Comley (1996), Gonier (1999), and Kwak and Radler (1999), among others, have underscored the depth and spontaneity of insights derived from open-ended surveys conducted through email and web platforms.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Is High Frequency Polling</title>
      <link>https://textprobe.io/posts/high-frequency-polling/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2024 05:02:05 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://textprobe.io/posts/high-frequency-polling/</guid>
      <description>Unlocking Public Opinion Faster: The Science Behind TextProbe Have you ever wondered how quickly public opinion can shift? Traditionally, gauging these changes relied on surveys – a process known for being slow and expensive. But what if there was a way to get real-time insights without sacrificing accuracy?&#xA;This is the core idea behind TextProbe, a method inspired by groundbreaking research published in the book Political Communication in Real Time. Here&amp;rsquo;s a glimpse into the science that makes TextProbe tick:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://textprobe.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 14:50:02 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://textprobe.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Meet Robert Edwardes: Your Data Analytics Partner With a proven track record in AI and machine learning, Robert Edwardes is your go-to expert for unlocking business insights. As the founder of TextProbe, Robert pioneers SMS solutions, blending AI and GIS for precision market research. From campaign management to data-driven strategies, Robert&amp;rsquo;s expertise spans nonprofits to political campaigns. With certifications in Azure and Scrum Master, trust Robert to elevate your analytics game.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://textprobe.io/services/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 14:50:02 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://textprobe.io/services/</guid>
      <description>Service Page: High Frequency Data Collection and Modeling At TextProbe, we specialize in high-frequency data collection and advanced modeling techniques to provide unparalleled insights into public sentiment and demographic understanding. Through innovative approaches and cutting-edge technology, we empower organizations to make informed decisions based on real-time data.&#xA;High Frequency Data Collection Using Mobile Phones for High-Frequency Data Collection: Mobile phones have revolutionized data collection, allowing for rapid and frequent surveys. We leverage mobile technology to gather real-time feedback from diverse demographics, enabling high-frequency monitoring of public opinion and trends.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get in Touch</title>
      <link>https://textprobe.io/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 14:50:02 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://textprobe.io/contact/</guid>
      <description>Curious about how text mining can benefit your business? Our team is here to help, whether you&amp;rsquo;re just getting started or need expert assistance with TextProbe. We can guide you through the process, answer your questions, and show you how to unlock the power of text data.&#xA;We&amp;rsquo;re passionate about helping businesses succeed. Let&amp;rsquo;s collaborate and use proven methods to improve your text-based campaigns and drive results. We look forward to hearing from you!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://textprobe.io/dnc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://textprobe.io/dnc/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://textprobe.io/policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://textprobe.io/policy/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://textprobe.io/signup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://textprobe.io/signup/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
