<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on TextProbe</title>
    <link>https://textprobe.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on TextProbe</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 18:38:04 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://textprobe.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Opened Quetion Powered by Natural Language Processing</title>
      <link>https://textprobe.io/posts/opened-and-nlpu/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 18:38:04 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://textprobe.io/posts/opened-and-nlpu/</guid>
      <description>Unleashing the Power of Open-Ended Questions in Surveys: A TextProbe Perspective In the realm of survey research, the debate between open-ended and close-ended questions has long been a topic of discussion. Over the years, numerous studies have highlighted the richness of responses garnered from open-ended questions, contrasting them with the more constrained nature of close-ended queries. Authors such as Comley (1996), Gonier (1999), and Kwak and Radler (1999), among others, have underscored the depth and spontaneity of insights derived from open-ended surveys conducted through email and web platforms.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Is High Frequency Polling</title>
      <link>https://textprobe.io/posts/high-frequency-polling/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2024 05:02:05 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://textprobe.io/posts/high-frequency-polling/</guid>
      <description>Unlocking Public Opinion Faster: The Science Behind TextProbe Have you ever wondered how quickly public opinion can shift? Traditionally, gauging these changes relied on surveys – a process known for being slow and expensive. But what if there was a way to get real-time insights without sacrificing accuracy?&#xA;This is the core idea behind TextProbe, a method inspired by groundbreaking research published in the book Political Communication in Real Time. Here&amp;rsquo;s a glimpse into the science that makes TextProbe tick:</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
